canadadrugpharmacy.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy Of CanadaDrugPharmacy.com

****  
---  
  
**Our Company**  
Canada Drug Pharmacy is about making quality medication accessible and better health possible. We are an online company that is based in Canada with an international network of fulfillment centers. Prices on the same medication vary between countries because they are set by the government of each individual country. Since prices of branded and generic version medicines are often cheaper in Canada and other countries, an online pharmacy company such as Canada Drug Pharmacy is able to always source from the location with the best prices. Read below for more details on [our company](http://www.canadadrugpharmacy.com/ourcompany.asp), timeframes for [shipping orders](http://www.canadadrugpharmacy.com/content/our-company/shipping.asp), and [privacy laws](http://www.canadadrugpharmacy.com/content/our-company/privacy.asp) that protect your information. 

**Privacy Policy**

All personal information submitted to CanadaDrugPharmacy.com via the Internet, phone, fax or mail is held in the strictest confidence. The information submitted is used by our staff, physicians, pharmacies, fulfillment centers, and contractors for the sole purpose of processing, dispensing, and delivering your prescriptions. Where authorized by you, we may also use this information to send you relevant marketing and promotional offers.

We will not furnish your personal information to an outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your prior consent. Notwithstanding the foregoing, in the event of a sale of all or substantially all of the assets of CanadaDrugPharmacy.com records containing personal information may be transferred to the purchaser.  
  
**Website Security**

CanadaDrugPharmacy.com provides security by offering 128 bit secure socket layer (128-bit SSL) encryption protection on its website through GeoTrust, a leading global provider of e-commerce security solutions. This high level of security helps protect you against identity theft and credit card fraud. CanadaDrugPharmacy.com has also implemented extensive security measures to protect your personal information from loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification or disclosure.  
  
**CanadaDrugPharmacy.com Email Spam Policy**

**CanadaDrugPharmacy.com has a zero-tolerance policy towards any form of spam email marketing.** We do not and have never engaged, directly or indirectly, in any form of spam email marketing. We adhere to very strict Federal, Provincial, and internal policies that prohibit any use of any form of spam email marketing. Furthermore, in accordance with our Privacy Policy, your information including email address is kept completely confidential and will not be sold or distributed to any other organization. 

While CanadaDrugPharmacy.com does utilize email to communicate with its existing customers for the strict purposes of order processing and general customer support, we do not send any emails for advertising or marketing purposes without your permission.   
  
POPULAR 

Drugs and Medicine (A-Z)

OUR COMPANY 

How To Order

  1. Search for your medication
  2. Add product into the shopping cart
  3. Proceed through our secure checkout.

###### Online Pharmacy Articles

Customer Service

**Toll-free Phone: 1-877-275-1525**  
Monday - Friday  5:00am - 10:00pm (PST)  
Saturday - Sunday  8:00am - 3:00pm (PST)

**Toll-free Fax: 1-877-558-5459**  
Our fax line is open 24 hours / 7 days

Copyright © 2003 - 2014 by CanadaDrugPharmacy.com - All rights reserved|
